http://www.iarugby.com/privacy

IA Rugby.com Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting IA Rugby.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
IA Rugby.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to IA Rugby.com, and understanding how visitors use our site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us here.
IA Rugby.com reserves the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Like IA on Facebook.
